hello bye you can hear me my name is
你好，你可以听到我的名字吗
Josiah and I
我和约西亚
I'm here to talk to you about some work
我在这里跟你谈一些工作
I've been doing kind of making single
我一直在做单身
page applications with spring security
具有Spring安全性的页面应用程序
and JavaScript and I've been using
和JavaScript，我一直在使用
angularjs in the front end a lot of what
前端的angularjs有很多功能
I'll say today is really about the
我会说今天真的是关于
architecture more about the actual tools
有关实际工具的架构
that the stack that I'm using if you
我正在使用的堆栈，如果您
have any small little questions that you
有任何小问题
think I should be able to answer as we
我认为我应该能够回答
go along just type them into the chat
继续输入聊天内容即可
and I have roblins from Spring Security
我有来自Spring Security的抢劫犯
and my friend Torsten Schmidt who is an
和我的朋友托尔斯滕·施密特（Torsten Schmidt）
angularjs expert from Germany they're on
来自德国的angularjs专家
the line and they can answer your
线，他们可以回答你
questions in text form if there's
文字形式的问题，如果有
anything really interesting we can save
任何我们可以保存的真正有趣的东西
it till the end but hopefully we can mop
直到最后，但希望我们能拖地
up a lot of small queries as we go along
我们进行很多小查询
okay so here's the agenda this is what I
好吧，这就是我的议程
will try and cover a really really quick
会尝试覆盖一个非常非常快的
introduction to the the elements of the
元素介绍
stack that I'm going to be talking about
我要谈论的堆栈
spring security spring session and
Spring Security 春季会议和
angularjs also spring cloud and the main
AngularJS也有春天的云和主要
thing will be to try to focus on what
事情将是尝试着重于什么
they need to do to be able to
他们需要做的是能够
communicate with each other so that you
互相交流，以便您
can use them in the most efficient way
可以最有效地使用它们
and in the most secure way so we're
以最安全的方式
going to focus on those features that
将专注于那些功能，
you need to build single page
您需要构建单页
applications that are secured in the
被保护的应用程序
backend using spring security and a lot
后端使用spring安全性和很多
of it is going to be to do with ether
这将与以太有关
about microservices right so it's gonna
关于微服务，所以它将
be about distributed systems and how you
关于分布式系统以及您如何
would implement security in such a
会在这种情况下实施安全性
system when you in particular when you
系统，当您特别是当您
have single page applications sitting
拥有单页应用程序
out on the front of your of your system
在您系统的前端
users to interact with so as you are
与您互动的用户
probably aware if you're not then you
可能知道你是否不是你
can follow the links and when we publish
可以关注链接以及我们发布时
the slides at the end so there's a blog
最后的幻灯片，所以有一个博客
series that I've been working on in
我一直在从事的系列
string dot IO so spring dot IO / blog
字符串点IO，所以弹簧点IO /博客
and you'll find a series of five blogs
您会发现一系列五个博客
that so far that I've been publishing on
到目前为止，我一直在发表
we're going to look at how at a high
我们将看看如何高
level at some of the sample apps that I
我在一些示例应用程序中的级别
presented in that series and we're going
在该系列中介绍，我们要
to use them for exploring the features
用它们来探索功能
basically if the systems that were
基本上，如果
building so spring security is the first
建设，因此Spring Security 是第一
intro introduction slide so this is as
简介幻灯片，如下所示
much as I'm going to say about what
正如我要说的
spring security is and then we'll see
Spring Security 是，然后我们将看到
some examples of it being used later on
稍后将使用的一些示例
so spring security is amongst other
所以Spring Security 是其中的一个
things a generic for a server based
基于服务器的通用
application it's a filter basically so
应用程序基本上是一个过滤器，所以
it's a filter based solution if you're a
如果您是
servlet application it is other things
servlet应用程序是其他东西
to other things and it covers
其他的东西，它涵盖了
authentication which is which is to say
身份验证即是说
the identity of the user or or
用户的身份或
protagonist he wants to use the system
他想使用该系统的主角
and authorization meaning access
和授权意味着访问
decisions at rules like you know the
像您知道的规则做出决定
user can access this resource if he is
用户可以访问此资源（如果他是
in the admin role that kind of that kind
在那种管理员角色中
of rule is implemented there's a short
规则实施了
shout-out here also for to because it's
在这里大声喊叫也是因为
a spring security module which I
我的弹簧安全模块
actually run myself and that's also very
真正让自己运行，这也非常
useful for this kind of system
对这种系统有用
especially if you're convinced that you
特别是如果您确信自己
need token-based authentication or if
需要基于令牌的身份验证，或者
you need single sign-on sorts of other
您需要其他种类的单点登录
features in spring security like I said
我说过的Spring Security 性功能
so go and look at the the webpage at the
所以去看看网页
bottom so you want to learn more
底部，所以您想了解更多
angularjs is I guess nearly half of the
我想angularjs是将近一半的
technology I'll be using in the rest of
我将在其余部分中使用的技术
the presentation it's a JavaScript
演示文稿是JavaScript
framework if you haven't met it before
框架，如果您以前从未遇到过
it's quite popular with the people like
在像这样的人中很受欢迎
me basically the Java Enterprise
我基本上是Java Enterprise
developers who are a little bit scared
有点害怕的开发人员
of JavaScript because it does things in
JavaScript的原因在于它在
a way that I kind of resonates I think
我认为这是一种共鸣的方式
with the sort of work that I do on the
与我在
server side so it does dependency
服务器端，所以它确实依赖
injection for instance and it has a sort
例如注射，它有一种
of MVC style model
MVC样式模型
approaching approach to to web pages a
接近网页的方法
lot of magic involved but once you've
涉及很多魔术，但是一旦
actually seen a few examples you can
实际上看到了一些例子，你可以
copy paste and be quite confident that
复制粘贴并非常有信心
it's you know we're going to work the
你知道我们要去工作了
way that you expected to it so I think
您期望的方式，所以我认为
that's probably why it's got so much
这可能就是为什么它有这么多的原因
traction in the enterprise however
然而，企业的牵引力
nothing about the architecture as I said
正如我所说的，关于架构的一切
of the app that I show here requires
我在这里显示的应用程序要求
angularjs it's just it's a quite a
angularjs这只是一个相当
common choice for people building that
人们的共同选择
kind of system with Java back ends with
带有Java后端的系统类型
spring I should also say all of the
春天我也应该说所有
angularjs I show you will be because I
我向您展示的angularjs是因为我
mean not an expert will be really basic
意味着没有专家会很基础
usage but I think is representative I
用法，但我认为代表我
think you can basically take that and
认为你基本上可以接受
expand it read the documentation which
展开阅读文档
is generally very good and he will get
通常很好，他会得到
where you need to go if you're a
如果你是一个需要去的地方
beginner if you're not hopefully
初学者，如果你不希望
recognize what I'm doing so the next
认识下我在做什么
thing I want to point out is that there
我想指出的是
are already quite a lot of features in
已经有很多功能
your browser that help you with this
您的浏览器可以帮助您
kind of thing so if you're writing an
这样的事情，所以如果你正在写一个
application web static resources in a
应用程序中的Web静态资源
browser you have these things already it
浏览器中已经有这些东西了
will give you for free HTTP basic
将为您提供免费的HTTP基本
authentication certificate based
基于认证证书
authentication there are features to
身份验证有功能
support Kerberos there are cookies very
支持Kerberos还有cookie
important shoutout for cookies because
重要的cookie喊叫，因为
that's what I'm going to be using a lot
这就是我将要使用的很多东西
in the the apps that I present either
在我展示的应用中
cause common operation resource sharing
导致通用操作资源共享
which is a way to protect applications
这是保护应用程序的一种方式
from accidentally loading code from
从意外加载代码
another site and you've got the strict
另一个网站，你有严格的
Transport Security which is a way to
运输安全是一种方法
force browsers to use the secure socket
强制浏览器使用安全套接字
layer and then finally an emerging thing
层，最后是新兴事物
you thought this thing called the
你以为这个东西叫做
content security policy and any of these
内容安全政策以及其中的任何一项
features that I'm going to really
我将要真正使用的功能
concentrate on today is the cookies but
今天只专注于饼干，但是
the text here is they're all in the
这里的文字是他们都在
browser they're reliable and free and
浏览器，它们可靠，免费，并且
you should use them as much as you can
你应该尽可能多地使用它们
without trying to you know build your
无需尝试就可以建立自己的
own solution to the same problems
自己解决同样的问题
okay so the next part of my stack which
好吧，所以我堆栈的下一部分
is going to be very important and if
将非常重要，如果
you've read the blog you can see where
您已经阅读了博客，可以看到
it fits into some of the existing apps
它适合一些现有的应用程序
spring session is a relatively new thing
春季会议是一个相对较新的事物
the Rob winched without last year
罗布没有去年就绞尽脑汁
scratching an itch I think that we'd all
挠痒痒，我想我们都会
had so we're very grateful to him it's
有，所以我们非常感谢他，这是
not specifically tied to spring security
与弹簧安全性无关
and actually that was sort of part of
实际上那是
the review process that we had
我们进行的审查过程
internally with some spring session we
在内部与一些春季会议，我们
decided that it needed to be more
决定需要更多
general than spring security but it does
一般比Spring Security ，但它确实
work well with it and what you get
与它一起工作以及您得到的
basically is really easy
基本上真的很容易
declarative distributed sessions and
声明式分布式会话和
distributed sessions are not something
分布式会话不是什么
that it's not a new concept it's
这不是一个新概念
something that Tom cabin you know bigger
你知道汤姆小屋的东西更大
application service authorities always
应用服务机构始终
supported it's just with this it just
支持它就是这样
makes it really easy and there is a
真的很容易，并且有一个
Redis implementation that works out of
Redis实现无法实现
the box and a single single interface
盒子和一个单一的接口
that you have to implement to add other
您必须实施以添加其他
back-end so it's very easy to to
后端，因此很容易
generalize but I think the final slide
一概而论，但我认为最后一张幻灯片
on my stack is about spring cloud so
在我的书架上是关于春天的云
spring cloud in a nutshell is a toolbox
简而言之，Spring Cloud是一个工具箱
for building micro services and building
用于构建微服务和构建
systems of micro services and one of the
微服务系统和
patterns that we implement or we make it
我们实现或实现的模式
easy to implement is a gateway or a
易于实施的是网关还是
reverse micro proxy I like to call it so
反向微代理，我喜欢这样称呼它
basically this is a reverse proxy where
基本上这是一个反向代理
you have a lot of control over the
您对
internal logic and that's quite a
内部逻辑，这相当
powerful tool to have in your in your
强大的工具
chest even if you're not building what
胸就算不建什么
you think of as a cloud system if you're
您认为您是一个云系统
building anything that's distributed
建立任何分布式的东西
then this reverse microbe proxy pattern
然后这个反向微生物代理模式
is actually very useful and I think I'll
实际上非常有用，我想我会
show you that today for the security use
告诉您今天用于安全用途
cases that we're looking at in addition
我们正在寻找的情况
if you're interested look at the links
如果您有兴趣，请查看链接
below and you'll find spring cloud
在下面，您会发现春天的云
covers things like a configuration
涵盖了类似配置的内容
management service discovery load
管理服务发现负载
balancing circuit breakers other things
平衡断路器其他
patterns basically bit of communication
模式基本上有点沟通
between nitrous services okay so
之间的亚硝酸服务好吗
slightly weird looking font on that side
在那边看起来有点奇怪的字体
is a table with an overview of the blog
是带有博客概述的表格
series that I've been doing so part 1
我一直在做的系列第1部分
through 6 part 6 hasn't been published
至第6部分第6部分尚未发布
yet but I've been working on it so we
但是，我一直在努力，所以我们
had sort of building after an
经过一段时间的建设
architecture building after system from
系统从
very simple up to distributed and more
非常简单，直到分布式等等
complex and so in part one it was a very
非常复杂，因此在第一部分中
simple single server containing all the
包含所有
resources static and dynamic with 8 just
静态和动态资源只有8个
with HTTP basic security nothing else
具有HTTP基本安全性
then we went in part 2 we added a login
然后在第2部分中，我们添加了登录名
form and so there's a bit more HTML in
表单，因此其中包含更多HTML
that a bit more Java Script in part 3 we
第3部分中的Java脚本要多一些
broke the session I broke the
打破了会议，我打破了
application down into multiple pieces
应用程序分为多个部分
and so now we have a resource server as
所以现在我们有一个资源服务器
well as the UI and the spring session to
以及用户界面和春季会议
tie those together to tie the
把那些绑在一起
authentication together and we used the
一起进行身份验证，我们使用了
session ID as an authentication token so
会话ID作为身份验证令牌，因此
the JavaScript had to actually send the
JavaScript必须实际发送
token to the resource server the next
下一个到资源服务器的令牌
I'll explain some of these in more
我将在其中详细说明其中一些
detail as we go through I'm just
细节，因为我们只是
summarizing in a minute the part for
一分钟总结一下
added this gateway proxy pass in at the
在处添加了此网关代理传递
top of the stack and I'll show you why
顶部，我将向您展示为什么
that's important with a picture in a
这一点很重要
minute and part 5 added or externalized
分钟，第5部分已添加或外部化
the authentication into a separate
认证成一个单独的
server so we used OAuth 2 to do single
服务器，因此我们使用了OAuth 2来完成
sign-on and then in part 6 what we're
登录，然后在第6部分中，我们将
going to do is add further done UI so in
要做的是添加进一步完成的UI，因此在
not just one UI but multiple different
不只是一个UI，而是多个不同的
applications all sitting behind the same
所有应用程序都位于同一个后面
gateway with granular and access rules
具有详细规则和访问规则的网关
managed by the individual back-end so
由个人后端管理，因此
that's the the high-level plan of what's
那是什么的高级计划
going to be in the next part of the
将在下一部分
series so in pictures the the basic
系列，所以图片中的基本
example that we we started this series
我们开始这个系列的例子
rod with lived like this he thought a
像这样生活，他想
browser sitting at the top loading
浏览器位于顶部
resources from an orange back-end that
来自橙色后端的资源
has both UI and API resources in it and
同时具有UI和API资源，并且
there's a link on the slide I had to put
幻灯片上有一个链接我必须放在
a
一种
ellipses in it but that's basically to
省略它，但这基本上是为了
github.com /d fire / spring security
github.com / d fire /Spring Security
angular and I'll show you the links to
有角度的，我将向您显示链接
everything at the end that's part one
最后的一切都是第一
and if I can I've seen I'll stick to the
如果可以的话，我会坚持
sides and I'll come back and show you
双方，我会回来告诉你
the code in the IDE in a minute the
一分钟内，IDE中的代码
basic building block for that is index
索引的基本构建块
dot HTML right so there's a static page
点HTML正确，因此有一个静态页面
that is served out of that orange blob
从那个橙色斑点里拿出来的
up into the browser it's very simple
进入浏览器非常简单
because I like to have something that
因为我喜欢吃点东西
fits on the slide it didn't it would
可以放在幻灯片上，不是吗
have fit on side if I left the header
如果我离开表头，可以放在一边
out but there's a there's a head in
出来，但是有头
there as well which I was mix it just
还有我把它混在一起的
for brevity which is style sheets
为了简洁，这是样式表
basically so omitting the style see I've
基本上省去了风格
got a body in my HTML I've got an in the
我的HTML中有一个正文，我的中有一个
body I've linked it to an angular
我已经将它链接到一个角度
application a module called hello which
应用一个名为hello的模块
I'll show you the implementation of in a
我将向您展示的实现
minute inside the body I've got a header
在身体的一分钟内，我有一个标题
and I've got a divs which contains a
我有一个包含一个
reference to another angular thing so an
提到另一个有角度的东西，所以
NG controller is basically a function
NG控制器基本上是一个功能
with with some special responsibilities
负有特殊责任
that I'll show you in a minute and the
一会儿给你看
key so this is this kind of MVC pattern
关键，这就是这种MVC模式
so this is a controller is called home
所以这是一个控制器叫做家
and the model contains an object called
并且模型包含一个名为
greeting and then I'm doing binding into
问候，然后我正在绑定到
the UI inside that div using greeting ID
div中使用问候ID的UI
greeting drop content with these handle
用这些句柄问候放下内容
bar markup markers so it's really I'm
酒吧标记标记，所以这真的是我
told it's not very efficient and you
告诉这不是很有效，你
shouldn't build big applications and
不应该构建大型应用程序，并且
complex logic this way but it's so
这样复杂的逻辑，但事实如此
simple even I can understand it so we
即使我能理解也很简单，所以我们
like that because it's easy to see
这样，因为很容易看到
what's going on when I show you the
当我告诉你这是怎么回事
JavaScript it'll be even easier and then
JavaScript，它将变得更加容易，然后
I've got two scripts to load at the
我有两个脚本要加载
bottom so one of them is the angular
底部，所以其中之一是角
library itself and I've mixed it in with
库本身，我将其与
some Twitter beef draft as well so that
一些Twitter牛肉草稿，以便
I can do some Styles did this in the
我可以做一些样式
same JavaScript
相同的JavaScript
and I've got my own application code in
而且我有自己的应用程序代码
a separate script hello dot J s on the
上的单独脚本问候点J s
next slide shows you hello da je yes
下一张幻灯片向您显示hello da je是的
it's completely minimal not trying to do
不尝试做是完全最小的
anything fancy here it's just to show
这里的任何花哨只是为了展示
you if you haven't seen angular before
如果你以前没见过角
that it's not actually that scary that's
实际上并不那么可怕
something like anybody can understand
任何人都可以理解的东西
here so I'm declaring a module called
在这里，我声明一个名为
hello and that was what I referred to in
你好，这就是我所说的
my body elements in the HTML containing
HTML包含的我的身体元素
just one thing in this case just one
在这种情况下只有一件事
controller called home and you define a
名为home的控制器，您定义了一个
controller using a function and the
控制器使用功能和
function takes arguments which are which
函数接受哪些参数
had fancy names right so these fancy
有好看的名字，所以这些好看的
names beginning with dollar are angular
以美元开头的名称是有角的
provided services and this is basically
提供服务，这基本上是
is what amounts to dependency injection
等于依赖注入
and its dependency injection by by name
并按名称注入依赖项
so there's a thing called scope which is
所以有一个叫做范围的东西
the variables inside the div here so the
div中的变量在这里，所以
div which has controls by the home
由家控制的div
controller has variables inside it
控制器内部有变量
called greeting and greeting is here
叫问候和问候在这里
scope greeting so scope is a local um
作用域问候语，所以作用域是本地um
namespace basically for variables inside
命名空间基本上用于内部变量
my um UI until the HTTP is the HTTP
我的用户界面，直到HTTP是HTTP
service provided by angular which I'm
我所提供的角度服务
using to do the get I'm going to get a
用做得到我将要得到
resource from a path slash resource and
路径斜杠资源中的资源和
if that's successful I take the data
如果成功，我将数据
from the response and I turn it into a
从响应，我把它变成一个
greeting so I'm getting JSON back from
问候，所以我从
that resource basically why don't we
该资源基本上为什么我们不
have a look at that in action I'm again
看看我在行动
see you could do this as well you could
看到你也可以做到这一点
clone the the project in github and then
在github中克隆项目，然后
it's all using maven so you can import
全部使用了Maven，因此您可以导入
into your favorite IDE which is what I'm
进入您最喜欢的IDE，这就是我
doing
在做
so where is it sorry cloud spring
那对不起云春
security angular that's the name of the
安全角就是
github repo and then there's a basic
github repo，然后有一个基本的
project which I can just import into
我可以导入的项目
this workspace I'll show you how simple
这个工作区，我会告诉你多么简单
it is it really is just the code that I
真的只是我的代码
just showed you there's an index.html
刚刚向您展示了一个index.html
with the stuff I just showed you there
我刚刚带你看的东西
there's the greeting being rendered
有问候被渲染
there's hello Jess which really is just
你好杰西，这真的只是
the code I just showed you there's a
我刚刚向您显示的代码有一个
tiny bitty animal here unless you know
除非你知道这里的小小动物
what oh it just says I can set the
哦，这只是说我可以设置
password for security right and then
安全权密码，然后
there's a java application which lets
有一个Java应用程序
show you the ball of because I don't
给你看球，因为我不
think I've got it on the slides it's a
认为我已经把它放在幻灯片上了
spring boot application so it says apps
spring boot 应用程序，所以它说应用程序
during boot application at the top and
在顶部启动应用程序时
it's an address controller because it's
这是一个地址控制器，因为它是
providing this resource path this
提供此资源路径
resource and the point so this the
资源和重点，所以这
resource endpoint returns a map so a map
资源端点返回地图，因此地图
of string two objects which just has the
字符串两个对象的
greeting in it so the greeting has an ID
问候语，这样问候语有一个ID
and there's some contents which is just
还有一些内容只是
six
六
hello it always says hello world but it
你好总是说你好世界，但是它
says it with a different unique
用另一种独特的方式说
identifier every time you load it and
每次加载标识符时，
this is amazingly a feature of all of
这是所有产品的惊人功能
the samples in the blog series just so
博客系列中的示例是如此
that they're easy to recognize and then
他们很容易识别，然后
I'm using string boots to main run the
我正在使用字符串引导程序主要运行
projects as a main so I just run that
项目作为主要项目，所以我只运行
agent see me do that did you I did it
特工看到我做到了，你做到了吗
Mike with my keyboard how do you run as
迈克（Mike）用我的键盘如何运作
Java that is it's running on port 8080
在8080端口上运行的Java
so I can go into my browser now and
所以我现在可以进入浏览器
actually you know I'm going to do I'm
其实你知道我要去做
going to do the smart thing and I'm
去做聪明的事，我
going to go new incognito window if you
如果您要进入新的隐身窗口
do this at home would do the same thing
在家做会做同样的事情
right and the first thing that happens
对，这是第一件事
is I get a prompt for easer name and
我是否得到提示，请输入化名
password so this is what they call HTTP
密码，所以这就是他们所说的HTTP
basic authentication and as my app
基本身份验证和作为我的应用程序
saying the ID and saying hello world
说出ID并问好世界
um I think that's probably enough for
嗯，我认为这足以
the basic sample actually want one more
基本样本实际上还想要一个
thing to show you before I switch off
在我关机之前给你看的东西
Liam out of the IDE - just to show you
Liam脱离IDE-只是向您展示
how easy that was
那是多么容易
I can almost do this live coding I just
我几乎可以完成这个现场编码
don't have time to type all the HTML
没有时间键入所有HTML
because nearly everything as you'll see
因为几乎所有您将看到的东西
in a minute is driven from the
一分钟后从
dependencies so I have an XML file
依赖项，所以我有一个XML文件
Palmdale XML which has spring boots
带有 spring boot 的Palmdale XML
darks and parents which makes things a
黑暗和父母，这使事情变得
bit easier because then I only have to
容易一点，因为那我只需要
define I don't have the defined versions
我没有定义的版本
here basically so I've got security web
基本上在这里，所以我有安全网
and some testing resources that's all I
还有我所有的测试资源
need to get a secure application working
需要让安全的应用程序正常工作
which is refreshingly simple ok so that
令人耳目一新的好吧，这样
was my basic application I added a
是我的基本应用程序，我添加了一个
sticky beef HTTP basic security and I
粘牛肉HTTP的基本安全性和我
showed you it working and I added that
向您展示了它的工作原理，我补充说
like I showed you using a dependency
就像我告诉你使用依赖
little typo there what I forgot to close
小错别字我忘了关闭
the XML properly but it's just a spring
XML正确，但这只是春天
boot start of security and all the
启动安全性和所有
starters do is pull in a curated set of
入门者要做的是挑选一组
transitive dependencies if you were
传递依赖（如果您是
doing it with dradle it would be very
用dradle做它会非常
similar ok so that was the base example
类似的好，所以这是基本示例
it has on the link between browser and
它在浏览器和
resource there I've got HTTP basic every
我在那里有HTTP基本资源
time I request a resource from the
当我从
server the browser sends the same HTTP
服务器浏览器发送相同的HTTP
basic authentication let me show you
基本身份验证让我告诉你
that in action
在行动
oops oops
哎呀
that's one ok
没关系
so therefore Network if I just reload
因此，网络，如果我只是重新加载
that page then here are all the requests
该页面，然后是所有请求
and responses going right so then in
响应正确，于是
your 300 not modified the most
您的300个修改最多的
interesting one here is the one - this
有趣的一个是一个-这个
resource which is coming back with hello
你好回来的资源
world which you can see there
你可以在那里看到的世界
the headers include a basic
标头包括一个基本
authentication so the browser knows that
身份验证，以便浏览器知道
it is going that once you've
一旦你完成了
authenticated once you've typed in that
在您输入后进行身份验证
username and password it can always send
可以随时发送的用户名和密码
that header and you will be
该标头，您将
authenticated which is really great
经过身份验证，这真的很棒
quite useful for getting something
拿东西很有用
started quickly okay but then what a lot
开始很快就可以了
of people actually prefer in terms of
的人实际上更喜欢
users prefer not to have that funny
用户宁愿不要那么有趣
little browser gray dialog box but to
小小的浏览器灰色对话框，但是
actually have a form in HTML that they
实际上有一个HTML形式
can fill in their credentials in and
可以在和中填写其凭据
this one we can see that it's because
我们可以看到这是因为
they liked the look of it another is
他们喜欢它的外观
because you can then extend it to do
因为你可以扩展它做
more than just user name password but
不只是用户名密码，而是
just sticking to the time being - the
只是暂时坚持-
username password use case we can we can
用户名密码用例我们可以
add a login form to that application
向该应用程序添加登录表单
quite easily and I did that in the blog
很容易，我在博客中做到了
actually in part two
实际上在第二部分
it should say part two at the bottom of
应该在第二部分的底部说
the slide and to do that I have to
幻灯片，要做到这一点，我必须
introduce some more spring security
引入更多弹簧安全性
configuration so what so far all I got
配置，到目前为止我得到了什么
is what I what I get out of the box from
这就是我从开箱即用中得到的
spring boot and here's a little recipe
spring boot ，这是一个小食谱
for how to add spring security I create
我如何创建弹簧安全性
an app configuration class in my
我的应用程序配置类
application and I make it extend web
应用程序，我让它扩展了网络
security configure it adapter and that's
安全配置它的适配器，那是
a callback basically from spring
基本上从春天开始的回调
security and it tells me I can configure
安全性，它告诉我可以配置
HTTP security and so the few things I
HTTP安全性以及我的一些东西
want to do are the HTTP basic that I've
想要做的是我已经拥有的HTTP基础
been using already and at the same time
一直在同时使用
I also want to say I want to create some
我也想说我想创造一些
access rules okay so I want to authorize
可以使用访问规则，所以我要授权
requests and I want to treat the static
请求，我想对待静态
resources index.html etc differently
资源index.html等不同
than anything else so these ones
比这些都重要
the home page basically in any login and
主页基本上是任何登录名，
home page resources than they need to
主页资源超出所需
load I'm going to say from it all so
负载，我要从这一切说
anybody's allowed to look at
任何人都可以看
those and anything else has to be
这些和其他任何东西都必须
authenticated and that just means that I
认证，这意味着我
can load a homepage and a login page and
可以加载主页和登录页面，以及
submit the credentials back to the HTTP
将凭据提交回HTTP
basic those of you who read the articles
基本的那些阅读文章的人
when they first came out I actually
当他们第一次出来时，我实际上
didn't use HTTP basic in the first
最初没有使用HTTP Basic
edition I used form login which is a
我使用表单登录的版本
different feature in spring security I
Spring Security 性I的不同功能
switched it to HTTP basic because it's
切换到HTTP基本，因为它是
the same as far as the clients concerned
就有关客户而言
is the same it's actually a little bit
是一样的，实际上是一点点
easier to set up on the JavaScript side
在JavaScript方面更容易设置
because you don't have to convert you
因为你不必转换你
don't have to convert data to form data
不必将数据转换为表单数据
from JSON which is what angular prefers
来自JSON的角度支持
so I switched to aged HTTP basic just
所以我切换到了陈旧的HTTP基本
seemed a bit easier to me to implement
对我来说似乎更容易实现
and the result is this so on the client
结果在客户端上是这样的
side you have in the HTML you have a new
您在HTML中拥有的一面
thing you have a login form and in the
事情，你有一个登录表格，并在
login form
登录表单
there's an ng submit so this says to
有一个ng提交，所以说
angular go and find when you when the
角去寻找当你何时
user submits this form going to find me
用户提交此表单以查找我
a function called login and execute that
一个名为登录并执行该功能的函数
function and so then I have to define
功能，所以我必须定义
the login function which I do inside my
我在内部执行的登录功能
angular application an ID that here so
角度应用程序的ID在这里
login is a function and it's dull
登录是一种功能，它很枯燥
descriptor login because this login is
描述符登录名，因为此登录名是
inside a controller inside my UI okay so
在我的UI内的控制器中，这样
then I define login in terms of another
然后我用另一个定义登录
function a utility function called
实用工具功能
authenticate and I define that somewhere
进行身份验证，然后在某处进行定义
else I haven't I need a definition but I
否则我不需要定义，但是我
can show you in the UI in a minute in
可以在一分钟内显示在用户界面中
the IDE in a minute so the authentic a
在一分钟内IDE就可以了
function sends HTTP basic credentials
函数发送HTTP基本凭证
and then checks the slash user endpoint
然后检查斜杠用户端点
which is in you endpoint I just added to
我刚刚添加到您的端点中
the application so I do use the HTTP
该应用程序，所以我确实使用HTTP
basic for the first request there what's
基本的第一个请求那里是什么
Pring security does in return is sends
Pring安全做为回报
me back a cookie and then subsequent
我退回一个cookie，然后再
requests from the browser to the the
从浏览器到
application code are authenticated by
应用程序代码由验证
that cookie
那个饼干
suspended spring security and browser
暂停的Spring安全性和浏览器
behavior they play nicely together they
他们在一起的行为很好玩
do what each one does what the other one
做每个人都做的另一件事
expects pretty much out of the box
开箱即用
one more thing okay before you can use
可以使用之前再做一件事
there you also need to tweak angular a
在那里，您还需要调整角度a
little bit okay so I said at the
有点好，所以我在
beginning spring security and angular
初春安全性和棱角分明
they both have all these nice features
他们都有这些漂亮的功能
they didn't quite speak the same
他们讲的不太一样
language you have to just sort of a lion
语言，你只需要一只狮子
expectations a little bit this is one of
期望一点，这是其中之一
the things you have to do in your
你必须要做的事情
angular module you can as well as
您可以以及
control as you can define config which
控制，因为你可以定义配置
is global for the whole application and
对于整个应用程序是全局的
in my config here I'm injecting HTTP
在我的配置中，我正在注入HTTP
provider and in HTTP provider I can set
提供程序，在HTTP提供程序中，我可以设置
default headers for all requests so all
所有请求的默认标头，因此所有
requests that come from angular to any
从角度到任何角度的要求
back-end basically using the dollar HTTP
后端基本上使用美元HTTP
service are going to have ex- requested
服务将被要求
with and then a special value XML HTTP
然后加上特殊值的XML HTTP
request so that's basically saying I am
要求，基本上就是说我是
Ajax in old fashioned 1997 language and
老式的1997年Ajax语言和
I see the feature of spring security it
我看到了弹簧安全的功能
used to be a feature of angular you
曾经是有角度的你的特征
didn't have to do this but they took it
不必这样做，但是他们接受了
out because I didn't think many back-end
出来，因为我不认为很多后端
frameworks actually understand what this
框架实际上了解这
means and spring security looks at it
手段和弹簧安全性看待它
and says oh you're not just a browser
说哦，你不只是浏览器
you're a script inside a browser so I
你是浏览器中的脚本，所以我
don't need to when I sent the 401
当我发送401时不需要
response because you're not
回应，因为你不是
authenticated I don't need to send www -
经过验证，我不需要发送www-
authenticate I'll just send a straight
验证，我将直接发送
401 an angular will then be able to
401一个角度将能够
interpret that fine the browser will
解释说浏览器会很好
then not pop up a dialogue with these
然后不弹出与这些对话
name password I think I probably do have
名称密码，我想我可能确实有
time just doing that quickly so I'll
时间只是快点做，所以我会
keep my basic because I might use it for
保持基本，因为我可能会用它
another demo in a minute and I'm going
一分钟后进行另一个演示，我要去
to import another
导入另一个
another project single from the blog
来自博客的另一个项目
series this is Patsy so now I felt not
系列这是帕特西，所以我现在感觉不
just index dot HTML but I've got two
只是索引点HTML但我有两个
fragments as well home and login dot
片段以及首页和登录点
HTML those are treated as templates so
将HTML视为模板，因此
in login dot HTML it's not a whole HTML
在登录点HTML中，它不是完整的HTML
page it's just a div with an error
页面只是一个有错误的div
message and a form user name/password
消息和表单用户名/密码
and in the java scripts which I'll just
在我将要使用的Java脚本中
show you quickly I've got some stuff to
告诉你我有很多东西要
do with routes which I haven't described
使用我未描述的路线
yet I've got the header common header
但是我有标题公共标题
and I've got the authenticate function I
我有身份验证功能
say that was the main thing I wanted to
说那是我想做的主要事情
show you so here in the authenticated
在经过身份验证的地方向您展示
function it takes credentials and an
功能需要凭证和
optional tool back and if the
可选工具，如果
credentials are there then it forms them
凭证在那里然后形成它们
into a basic authentication header so
进入基本的身份验证标头
this is v2 a thing it's just a
这是v2，只是
JavaScript primitive which you have in
您拥有的JavaScript原语
your browser basically and let me just
您的浏览器基本上让我
run it so the java application is very
运行它，因此Java应用程序非常
similar to the one we've seen already
与我们已经看到的相似
except it also has this slash user
除了它也有这个斜杠用户
endpoint and somebody pointed out and
终点，有人指出
comments in the blog that this is a very
博客中的评论说这是一个非常
dumb and basic implementation of these
这些的愚蠢和基本实现
at endpoint if you were doing it for
在端点上（如果您这样做）
real you probably wouldn't do it just
真的，你可能不会这样做
like this you would probably return it
这样你可能会退还
so these are not just the whole user
所以这些不只是整个用户
because you wouldn't want to reveal
因为你不想透露
everything about it but this is fine to
关于它的一切，但这对
get it started so let me just run this
开始吧，让我运行
not it explicitly this time instead of
这次不是明确地代替
using the keyboard
使用键盘
runners to have application I will hit
跑步者申请我会打中
sure hope I I'm not still running the
肯定希望我还没有运行
other one which I am hang on ok don't
我挂着的另一只好别
like it did I get there in time no I
就像我能及时到达那里
didn't get there in time
没有及时到达
ok I'll run this one again if they were
好吧，如果他们
going to crash on port 8080 so I have to
会在端口8080上崩溃，所以我必须
run one at a time
一次跑一个
there it is running on port 8080 so my
那里在端口8080上运行，所以我的
my the browser window I'm not going to
我的浏览器窗口我不会
use this one I'm going to do the smart
用这个我要聪明
thing again I'm going to use a new
再说一遍，我要使用一个新的
incognito window okay so now I've got
隐身窗口好了，现在我有了
I'm not authenticated so in my angular
我没有通过身份验证
app is not showing me anything
应用没有显示任何内容
interesting I have to log in to see my
有趣的是我必须登录才能看到我的
greeting I'm going to say user password
问候，我要说出用户密码
I'm gonna open up the developer console
我要打开开发者控制台
before I do that there's my greeting
在我这样做之前，有我的问候
okay and if we look at what just happens
好吧，如果我们看看发生了什么
there's the call to the user endpoint
有到用户端点的呼叫
and that's basically the one which is
基本上就是那个
authenticating so when that comes back
进行身份验证，以便何时返回
it goes in with basic credentials
它带有基本凭证
actually goes in with a cookie okay so
其实还可以带一个饼干，所以
that you didn't see the authentication
您没有看到认证
they think the authentication core where
他们认为认证核心在哪里
the authentication tool is just a call
身份验证工具只是一个电话
to slash user and then this is cool for
削减用户，然后这很酷
the resource and point which is same as
资源和点与
the basic example okay so I needed that
基本示例好吧，所以我需要
special header in all the browser
所有浏览器中的特殊标头
requests just to stop the dialog from
要求只是停止对话框
being popped up by the browser there's a
被浏览器弹出，有一个
summary of what's happening there the
那里发生的事情的摘要
browser sends HTTP basic when it first
浏览器第一次发送HTTP基本信息
authenticates and it gets back a cookie
进行身份验证并返回Cookie
in return and then on subsequent
作为回报，然后在随后
requests it always sends the cookie why
要求它总是发送cookie，为什么
is that a good thing because that's what
那是一件好事，因为那是什么
browsers do they always send cookies and
浏览器是否总是发送Cookie和
so you don't have to write any code so
因此您不必编写任何代码，因此
my recommendation is to find a way for
我的建议是找到一种方法
that to work basically and that's what
基本上可以正常工作，这就是
we do with the rest of the samples okay
我们会处理其余的样本
so quick word about cross-site request
关于跨站点请求的简短信息
forgery another thing that is very
伪造另一件事
important obviously you want to stop it
重要的是显然您想停止它
happening term spring security and
春季学期安全
angularjs both have good support for
angularjs都对
cross-site request forgery protection
跨站点请求伪造保护
they don't quite do Dan
他们不太喜欢Dan
way so here's a summary of what they do
这样，这里是他们所做的摘要
spring security sends the token it
Spring Security将令牌发送给它
requires a token to be to be attached to
需要将令牌附加到
the session and for that token to be
会话，并且该令牌为
attached to requests when the client
当客户端附加到请求
sends a request it has to attach a token
发送一个必须附加令牌的请求
spring security tells the client about
Spring Security向客户讲述
the token in a request attribute by
请求属性中的令牌
default or named underscore Caesars and
默认或命名为下划线的Caesars和
then from the client in the request that
然后从客户的要求中
expects a header called
需要一个标题
X minus C surf token
X减C冲浪令牌
whereas angular it likes to accept the
而有角度的它喜欢接受
cookie the the token value as a cookie
cookie令牌值作为cookie
they like the cookie to be called the
他们喜欢将Cookie称为
excess excess RS not CSRF and then when
过量过量RS不是CSRF，然后何时
when the client sends a header it should
客户端发送标头时，应该
be X minus X s RF not X minus C SRS so
是X减去X的RF，而不是X减去C SRS，所以
they don't quite talk to each other but
他们彼此不交谈，但是
we can fix that so we can we can add a
我们可以解决该问题，以便我们可以添加一个
little bit of configuration to spring
弹簧的一点点配置
security to support this angular naming
支持此角度命名的安全性
convention I prefer to do it that way
约定我更喜欢那样做
because I understand less of the client
因为我不太了解客户
side so I want the client just to work
一边，所以我希望客户只是工作
out of the box you could hear the other
开箱即用，您可以听到另一个
way you could just use spring security
您可以仅使用Spring Security的方式
out of the box and trying that angular
开箱即用，尝试一下
to it but it would involve Ashley that
对此，但涉及Ashley
would involve sending rendered content
将涉及发送渲染的内容
from the server so it wouldn't really be
从服务器，所以它不是真的
a static web application anymore you'd
您将不再需要静态Web应用程序
need to sort of sort of an endpoint to
需要某种端点
capture the token value
捕获令牌值
anyway the easiest thing to do at least
无论如何，最容易的事至少
in my view is to make spring security
我认为是为了确保Spring Security
just send the right data to angular so
只是将正确的数据发送到angular
here we in our web security
在这里，我们在我们的网络安全中
configurative apps and the same things
配置应用程序和相同的东西
we looked at before and the configure
我们之前看过
methods when we finish doing the other
当我们完成另一种方法时
stuff that we did the authorization the
我们授权的东西
access rules then we start configuring
访问规则，然后我们开始配置
thesis and one of the Caesar features is
论文和凯撒特色之一是
you can add a token repository and this
您可以添加令牌存储库，
token repository is the same as the
令牌存储库与
default one but it has a different
默认值，但有一个不同的值
header name so that's all taken care of
标头名称，因此已全部处理
one half of the problem the other half
问题的一半，另一半
of the problem the fact that the angular
问题的事实是
expects a cookie
期待一个cookie
I'm going to do in this case with a
在这种情况下，我将使用
custom filter so I'm going to say to
自定义过滤器，所以我要说的是
spring security app please add a filter
Spring Security 应用，请添加过滤器
after the sea sir filter please add this
海先生过滤器后，请添加此
custom filter sea surf header filter and
自定义过滤器海浪头过滤器和
that is the implementation is missing
那是实现的缺失
but that is basically a filter that
但这基本上是一个过滤器
sends that's a cookie to the client if
如果是的话，发送一个cookie给客户端
if the c v token has changed then it
如果简历令牌已更改，那么它
will send a cookie xsrf token and that's
将发送一个cookie xsrf令牌，这是
all you need to get it working I'm
所有你需要使它工作我
working with winds hopefully we can make
希望我们能与风合作
this a little bit more kind of
这有点多
declarative a bit more out of the box in
声明式的开箱即用
spring security 4.0 and if you shirley's
Spring Security 4.0，如果您是shirley's
at least anyway so it up to spring
至少无论如何，直到春天
security 3.2 you could make it work like
安全3.2，你可以让它像
this and that's the way that the samples
这就是样本的方式
work in the blogs okay so the next thing
在博客上工作好吧，接下来
I did in the blogs was I split the UI
我在博客中所做的就是拆分UI
NCT a-- so I took the UI static
NCT a--所以我将UI设为静态
resources and the resource server the
资源和资源服务器
resort endpoint
度假村终点
I put the resource endpoint in a
我将资源端点放在
separate server so this picture I'm
单独的服务器，所以这张照片我
showing you here is the vanilla sample
向您展示的是香草样品
application which was used in part three
第三部分中使用的应用程序
of the blog series there are actually
博客系列中实际上有
two apps in part three the first one was
第三部分中的两个应用程序，第一个是
vanilla and it worked like this it had
香草，它像这样工作
HTTP basic to the UI and just like the
HTTP基本的UI，就像
the one that we just attached the login
我们刚刚附上登录名的那个
page one and it also had HTTP basic to
第一页，它还具有HTTP基本功能
the resource services using the same
使用相同的资源服务
credentials basically for the for the
凭证主要用于
back-end and in also in part three what
后端，还有第三部分
we did was we introduced spring session
我们所做的是我们介绍了春季会议
so this is a really neat thing you can
所以这是一件非常整洁的事情
do your one really neat thing you can do
做一件你可以做的很整洁的事情
see you can scale those applications up
看到您可以扩大这些应用程序
in the previous site you can scale as
在上一个站点中，您可以扩展为
I've been a couple ways one would be to
我曾经有过几种方式
use a load balancer with sticky sessions
使用带有粘性会话的负载均衡器
and another one would be to distribute
另一个是分发
the session data so we do the distribute
会话数据，所以我们进行分发
the session date a bit using Redis and
会话日期使用Redis和
spring session and like I said at the
春季会议，就像我在
beginning that spring session comes
春季会议开始
a very easy way to do this with a single
一个简单的方法可以做到这一点
annotation and just a register in the
注释和只是一个寄存器
backend so in this case what we have is
后端，在这种情况下，我们拥有的是
a browser which sends HTTP basic for the
一个浏览器，它为
first request and then gets the cookie
首先请求，然后获取Cookie
and uses and subsequent requests to the
以及对
UI and then for the resource server what
UI，然后对于资源服务器是什么
we did was we turned every request into
我们所做的就是将每个请求都转化为
the resource of and we added a header
的资源，我们添加了标题
which is kind of an authentication token
这是一种身份验证令牌
and the token value was the cookie and
令牌值是cookie和
the same Valley was the cookie so we had
那个山谷是饼干，所以我们有
to add we had to make that cookie
添加，我们必须制作该Cookie
visible to angular and there was some
可见到有角的，有一些
code to write to do that so the the the
编写代码来做到这一点的
application is now lovely and scalable
应用程序现在很可爱且可扩展
but it did have a few little sort of
但确实有一些
wrinkles in it to do is extracting the
它要做的皱纹是提取
50 value and making it into a token the
50值并将其变成令牌
fact the spring session handles the
春季会议处理
storage of it and distribution of it
存储和分发
means that I can scale everything now
意味着我现在可以扩展一切
perfectly but I did there is little bit
完美，但我做到了
of overhead cognitive and maintenance
的认知和维持
overhead in the the server and the
服务器和服务器的开销
client I've saved this application so
客户我已保存了此应用程序，因此
there was the the basic spring session
有一个基本的春季会议
sample the next thing I did in the blog
样本我在博客中做的下一件事
was in part 4 we introduced the Gateway
在第4部分中，我们介绍了网关
pattern and the benefit of the Gateway
模式和网关的好处
pattern you can basically see if I sit
你基本上可以看到我坐的模式
between those two slides so it's the
在这两张幻灯片之间
same set of components the same
同一组组件相同
responsibilities but the architectures
责任，但架构
whoops sorriest it the wrong way the
抱歉，错误的方式是
architecture slightly different so I'm
架构略有不同，所以我
going to flick between them now Gateway
现在要在它们之间滑动
not gateway gateway not gateway and the
不是网关，不是网关，
difference is with the gateway all the
与网关不同的是
requests from the browser
来自浏览器的请求
go through the gateway that's why it's
通过网关，这就是为什么
called a gateway so you can do that nice
叫做网关，所以你可以做得很好
thing that we did with the login page
我们对登录页面所做的事情
application the single page application
应用单页应用
at the beginning in part two in fact you
实际上，在第二部分的开头
can do HTTP basics for the
可以为
authentication then use the cookie from
身份验证，然后使用来自
then on and all the request goes
然后所有的请求
the Gateway and so the Gateway just lays
网关，所以网关只是奠定
that out basically and hands it to the
基本上把它交给
back end I'm just using exactly the same
后端，我只是使用完全相同的
cookie header basically so the resource
Cookie标头基本上是资源
server as far as he knows is just
据他所知，服务器只是
getting a cookie from a browser it just
从浏览器获取cookie
happens to be coming by her a reverse
碰巧由她来了
proxy and the way that we implemented
代理以及我们实施的方式
this was using spring cloud I think what
这是使用春天的云，我想
I'm going to do is yeah I'll just walk
我要做的是，我会走路
through the examples until I get to a
通过示例，直到我进入
point where I want to jump out and do a
我要跳出来做一个
demo I'll show you I'll come back to
演示我会告诉你，我会回到
that example ok so then in plus five I
这个例子好吧，然后再加上五个我
took the Gateway and the resources
占用了网关和资源
basically from exactly the same pattern
基本上从完全相同的模式
from part four and we all waited with
从第四部分开始，我们都在等待
the externalize the authentication so
外部化身份验证
instead of just authenticating with HTTP
而不是仅通过HTTP进行身份验证
basic it was a separate server but did
基本，这是一个单独的服务器，但
that call the authorization server it
调用授权服务器
was noble two and spring security OAuth
当时是高贵的两位，并且是Spring Security OAuth
2 implementation so you basically have
2实施，所以你基本上有
two cookies in the browser one for the
浏览器中的两个Cookie，一个用于
both server which it's kind of an SSO
都是SSO的两个服务器
token so you could use that to log in to
令牌，因此您可以使用该令牌登录
any number of applications and we just
任何数量的应用程序，我们只是
used one and then that authentication
使用一个，然后进行身份验证
process would generate a cookie for the
流程将为
gateway and then the Gateway will hand
网关，然后网关将移交
that down to the resource server there
一直到那里的资源服务器
was sorry it would doesn't hand the
很抱歉，它不会交给
resource to cookie dancers also he
饼干舞者的资源也是他
didn't need string session this one you
不需要这个字符串会话你
could use it for the cookies if you
可以将其用于Cookie，如果您
wanted to but the gateway in this case
想要但在这种情况下的网关
is passing the oauth2 token
正在传递oauth2令牌
I'm sorry down into the resource server
我很抱歉进入资源服务器
okay so this is the one where I might
好吧，这是我可能会
break out into a demo so let's for the
进入演示，让我们来
sake of argument let's say we want to
为了争辩，我们要
play a slightly different game rearrange
玩略有不同的游戏重排
things a little bit differently so that
事情有点不同，所以
instead of the gateway in the UI being
而不是UI中的网关
in the same component let's say we want
在同一组件中，假设我们要
to break the Gateway out into a separate
将网关分解为单独的
component and leave the backend well in
组件并将后端留在
this picture is a single single resource
此图片是单个单一资源
but obviously you could start as soon as
但显然您可以尽快开始
you've got the gateway in place you can
您已经准备好了网关
then split up the backend and do it in
然后拆分后端并进行
different ways so I'm going to show you
不同的方式，我将向您展示
that basically by well I'll make the
基本上，我会做
observations first that this UI plus
首先观察到这个UI加上
resource thing in the bottom of the
底部的资源物
screen bottom of the screen here is
屏幕的屏幕下方是
basically identical to the first
与第一个基本相同
application we ever rode the basic one
应用我们曾经骑过最基本的
and so if I can just take that basic
所以如果我能接受这个基础
sample and put a very simple gateway in
样本并在其中放置一个非常简单的网关
front of it I will have achieved my
在它的前面，我将实现我的
objective so let's see how I'm going to
客观的，让我们看看我将如何
do that so how I'm going to do that is
这样做，所以我要怎么做
I'm going to use oops I'm not going to
我要使用哎呀，我不会
use f12 I'm going to use a new tab I'm
使用f12我要使用一个新标签
going to use a new tab to go to this
将使用一个新的选项卡转到此
initializer application which some of
初始化应用程序中的一些
you might be seen with might have seen
您可能会看到与可能已经看到
before this one is a little bit
在此之前一点
different because it is flat spring
不同，因为它是板簧
cloud aware so it's actually a spring
意识到云，所以实际上是春天
cloud based initializer not just a
基于云的初始值设定项
spring boot so here I can add all of the
spring boot ，所以在这里我可以添加所有
cloudy stuff cloud patterns and the one
多云的东西云模式和一个
I want I'm interested in is zoo because
我想对动物园感兴趣，因为
he's the gatekeeper I don't need to add
他是我不需要添加的网守
web because that's included in zoo but I
网络，因为它包含在动物园中，但是我
do want to have security so there's a
确实想拥有安全性，所以有一个
zoo and security and Redis I would add
动物园和安全性以及Redis，我会添加
spring session as it was here but it
春天的会议，因为它在这里，但它
isn't so I'll generate a code I generate
不是，所以我将生成我生成的代码
a project here let's call Gateway dog
这里的一个项目叫Gateway dog
zip open that up and so that's just a
拉链打开它，所以这只是一个
maiden maiden project in there look and
处女处项目
so I'll extract that and then I'll go to
所以我将其提取出来，然后去
my IDE and I'll import it let me see
我的IDE，我将其导入让我看看
they need the single one anymore but I'm
他们不再需要一个，但我
keeping the basics that I actually want
保持我真正想要的基础
to actually what I'll do with basic is
实际上，我将要使用的基本功能是
I'll copy it okay so I'm making a copy
我会复制的，所以我要复制
of basic and I'm calling it demo so I
基本的，我称之为演示，所以我
don't mess with the existing basic I'll
不要搞砸现有的基本
just delete basic
只需删除基本
okay so I've got this new project called
好，所以我有一个新项目叫做
demo and then I'm going to import the
演示，然后我将导入
gateway from my downloads directory okay
我的下载目录中的网关好
so here's my gateway I'm going to one
所以这是我要进入的网关
string session so I need to add that
字符串会话，所以我需要添加
dependency I've got my Zul red it's
依赖我让我的祖尔红了
security stuff already I'm just gonna
安全的东西我已经要
add spring session and I want the
添加春季会议，我想
release version okay so that's that done
发行版本好，就这样完成了
and then in my main application I'm just
然后在我的主要应用程序中
going to at enable tool proxy and at
转到启用工具代理和
enable Redis HTTP so this is the string
启用Redis HTTP，所以这是字符串
cloud thing setup Azul so endpoint and
云事物设置Azul，以便端点和
this is the spring session thing so that
这是春季会议的事情
that's in terms of Java code that I've
这就是我所用的Java代码
finished all I need to do actually is
完成我实际上要做的就是
I'm going to rename this file has
我要重命名这个文件有
application llamo because the annals
之所以申请llamo，是因为
easier to work with so this so I'm going
更容易合作，所以我要
to add either password password so I
添加任何一个密码，所以我
know how to login I'm going to say
知道如何登录我要说的
something about session creation I think
我认为有关会话创建的一些事情
always is is enough definitely I I'm a
永远够了，绝对是我，我是
kid maybe do it with a different one but
孩子也许用另一种来做，但是
I have to fish off the default session
我必须取消默认会话
creation policy and then I have to do
创建策略，然后我必须做
now to set up the routes in the proxy
现在在代理中设置路由
basically says all routes as a URI which
基本上说所有路由都是URI，
is HTTP localhost let's call it 80 81
是HTTP本地主机，我们称之为80 81
all right um so yeah okay so I think I
好吧，嗯，是的，所以我想我
know I know I need to do another thing
知道我知道我需要做另一件事
that um that's fine so I can run this
那个很好，所以我可以运行这个
app on port 8080 okay so run as spring
端口8080上的应用程序正常，因此可以在春季运行
do app it run as java application
做它作为Java应用程序运行的应用程序
whatever I'll do it I'll do it I'll take
我会做的我都会做的
either alright so I wasn't nearly
要么都好，所以我离
running it's running I can show you so I
运行它，我可以告诉你，所以我
don't have anything to doesn't have any
没有什么就没有
backends yet but I can show you what its
后端，但我可以告诉你它的
roots are so there's an endpoint in
根是有一个端点
there called roots it has basic
有所谓的根它有基本
authentication how does a box because
验证框如何，因为
it's spring security and there's my root
春天的安全，这是我的根源
oh is that wrong and I sign you out then
哦，那是错的，然后我将您注销
you there's a reason it's you that
你是有原因的
because I've specified this wrong
因为我指定了这个错误
somehow it's all routes URL thank you
不知何故，这是所有路线的URL谢谢
I'm gonna restart that
我要重启
okay it's my roots again all right
好吧，这又是我的根
so now anything I sent to /ui a flash
所以现在我发送给/ ui的任何内容
you I flashed after will go to 80 81 and
你我闪过之后会去80 81
of course there's nothing there at the
当然，那里什么都没有
minute so if I do it I should get an
分钟，所以如果我这样做，我应该得到一个
arrow yeah connection refused because
箭头是连接被拒绝是因为
there isn't one
没有一个
slightly ugly error but that's what it
有点难看的错误，但这就是它
is so then to make something appear on
如此便使某物出现在
port 8081
端口8081
I'm going to take this existing single
我要把这张单曲
page application I'm going to remove the
页面应用程序，我将删除
default passwords okay but I'm going to
默认密码可以，但是我要
add a session creation policy and a
添加会话创建策略和
server port 8081
服务器端口8081
so that things now going to be running
这样事情就可以运行了
there I'm just going to check one thing
那里我只是要检查一件事
quickly so when it goes to its resource
快速，所以当它去资源
it's a relative resource not an absolute
这是相对资源，而不是绝对资源
one which is fine because I want it to
一个很好，因为我想要它
be relative to the proxy root okay so I
相对于代理根好吧，所以我
just with this one I basically just have
我基本上只有这个
to add that spring session thing so
添加那个春季会议的东西，所以
securities I want spring session 1 0 and
我想要春季证券1 0和
spring data starter Redis okay so with
spring数据启动器Redis还可以
those two things in my existing UI
我现有的用户界面中的这两件事
application I'm just gonna this is the
应用程序，我只是这是
same one we used before the basic one
我们在基本版本之前使用的相同版本
enable Redis HTTP session and then if I
启用Redis HTTP会话，然后如果我
run this app everybody trust their
运行这个程序，每个人都相信他们
fingers
手指
so that's running and it's running with
所以它正在运行，并且与
HDTV basic but with a default security
HDTV基本但具有默认安全性
setup which is a random password so I
设置，这是一个随机密码，所以我
don't know what that password is I won't
不知道那个密码是我不会
be able to log into that application
能够登录该应用程序
except through the proxy and let's hope
除了通过代理，让我们希望
that this is the proxy that's
这是代理
authenticating yes okay so what I did
身份验证是好的，所以我做了什么
but there was I authenticated with my
但是我有我的身份验证
password password to the proxy and the
密码代理和密码
proxy passed the request back through to
代理将请求传递回给
the backend the proxy remember is
代理记住的后端是
completely empty there's no HTML or
完全为空，没有HTML或
JavaScript in it okay so that just
可以使用JavaScript，这样就可以了
basically showed you how simple it was
基本上告诉你这是多么简单
to set up a gateway that's a bit of a
设置一个有点
trivial gateway but it shows you you
平凡的网关，但它告诉你
know how you can open unlock that
知道如何打开解锁
potential you can start now adding
您现在就可以开始添加的潜力
features to it and one thing you might
功能和一件事，你可能会
do the first step would be to break
要做的第一步是打破
apart the backend again so the UI might
再次分开后端，因此用户界面可能
live in a separate resource from the API
与API位于不同的资源中
resources and then you could multiply
资源，然后您可以乘以
those and then finally we might be able
这些，然后我们也许能够
to get to the point where we have a part
达到我们参与其中的地步
six in the blog and that will look like
博客中有六个，看起来像
this so I started work on this this
这个，所以我开始做这个
encoding github already and the idea
已经编码github和想法
behind that was you have a gateway which
在那后面是一个网关
isn't as dumb or basic as the one I just
不像我刚才那样愚蠢或基本
showed you actually have some HTML in it
显示您实际上有一些HTML
so it has the login form in it so you
因此它具有登录表单，因此您
can log in through the Gateway and then
可以通过网关登录，然后
it has its really basic navigation so
它具有非常基本的导航功能，因此
the navigation tells the user that he
导航告诉用户他
has a available UI application or maybe
有可用的UI应用程序，或者
more than one UI application so this one
一个以上的UI应用程序
has a UI application which is for users
有一个针对用户的UI应用程序
in green there and another one an admin
以绿色显示，另一个为管理员
application which also has a user
也有一个用户的应用程序
interface which is for admin users and
适用于管理员用户的界面，以及
the admin users are also split between
管理员用户也分为
readers and writers so in part 6 or we
读者和作家，所以在第6部分中
get into is some fairly realistic use
进入是相当现实的使用
cases where you have access rules which
您拥有访问规则的情况
are quite granular and the only place
非常细致，唯一的地方
that you should know about those
你应该知道的那些
granular rules are in the backend
精细的规则在后端
components and
组件和
and so the key to that is again spring
所以关键是春天
session sharing an authentication token
会话共享认证令牌
amongst all the application components
在所有应用程序组件中
so they all basically share the same
所以他们基本上都共享相同的
user data and they can see their roles
用户数据，他们可以看到自己的角色
but they make their own decisions based
但是他们根据自己的决定
on the roles and in a realistic gateway
在角色和现实网关中
what you would have here is also a
您在这里所拥有的也是
back-end database for the user data so
后端数据库中的用户数据，因此
you probably have like an Active
你可能有一个活跃的
Directory or maybe a relational database
目录或关系数据库
MongoDB something like that behind the
MongoDB之类的东西
Gateway containing user data and then
网关包含用户数据，然后
that would be shared out through the
将通过
Redis cache basically so that will be
Redis缓存基本上是这样
part six
第六部分
I won't go in try and show you all of
我不会尝试向您展示所有
that code today but that's basically it
今天的代码，但基本上就是
from from from today's presentations a
从今天的演讲中
bunch of links here the slides that I've
一堆链接，这里是我的幻灯片
been showing ha here in Prezi sicom you
在Prezi sicom中向您展示ha
can find a link in there I will get them
可以在那里找到一个链接，我会得到他们的
on PDF and into speaker deck at some
在PDF上并进入扬声器甲板
point but I'm having trouble printing
点，但我在打印时遇到问题
them in there so watch out for those in
他们在那里，所以要小心那些
a couple of days probably the github
几天可能是github
repo with all the code is this one so
所有代码的仓库就是这个
it's desire Springs security angular I
渴望斯普林斯安全角我
may turn that into a bunch of plugins at
可能会变成一堆插件
some point but at the minute it's just
某些时候，但在一分钟
sample code there is the spring security
示例代码中有spring安全性
force projects there that I run there's
强制在那里我运行的项目
plenty of spring cloud actually in cloud
大量的春天云实际上在云中
spring dot IO actually think that that
Spring dot IO实际上认为
URL might be wrong slash by clicking on
通过单击，URL可能是错误的斜杠
it so your hands I know that's fine that
所以你的手我知道那很好
works ok so um the spring cloud Netflix
可以正常工作，以便春天云Netflix
there are other vistas spring cloud that
还有其他远景春天的云，
you can get you from the root URL there
你可以从那里的根URL
the Netflix piece is where you get at
Netflix就是您的去处
enable Zul proxy so that's just the the
启用Zul代理，因此
correct pendency to include basically if
正确地将其包括在内
you wanted to do that I used to start at
你想做我以前开始的事情
a spring cloud starter as clouds spring
像云一样的春天
clouds that Azul
蔚蓝的云
here's the first link the first blog and
这是第一个博客的第一个链接，
from there you can click through to the
从那里您可以点击进入
first five that were published here's my
我发表的前五个是我的
chat handle in case you want to moan at
聊天句柄，以防您抱怨
me if you want to do more than a hundred
我，如果你想做一百多个
and forty characters moaning then please
然后四十个字符mo吟
send me an email and that's it thank you
给我发送电子邮件，就是这样，谢谢
very much hey Dave sorry about that I've
非常嘿，戴夫对不起
stuck on mute there for a second oh yeah
卡在静音那里一秒钟哦，是的
yeah you got me yeah great thank you so
是的，你得到了我，很好，谢谢你
much this is great so yeah all the
这太好了，是的，所有
follow-up links right there fabulous um
后续链接就在那里
we're just chasing down the last couple
我们只是追逐最后一对
questions here I think we've pretty much
这里的问题我想我们已经很多了
attended to all of them I think one of
我参加了所有人
the last ones probably is for Rob the
最后一个可能是罗伯
perennial question that I always see
我经常看到的常年问题
whenever security is mentioned people
每当提到安全问题时，人们
asking about CAS versus Roth but I don't
询问CAS与Roth的关系，但我没有
know if that's one you want to take a
知道那是不是你想要的
whack at but I see that a lot whenever
重击，但我看到很多
there's a spring security-related
Spring Security 相关
yeah I know captures a nice a nice
是的，我知道捕捉一个好
system test is a single sign-on protocol
系统测试是单点登录协议
for those who aren't familiar with it
对于那些不熟悉它的人
it's quite common in the academic world
这在学术界很普遍
it's a nice open source project we're
这是一个很好的开源项目
friendly with the guys who run it and we
与运行它的人友好，我们
occasionally try and hire them and yeah
偶尔尝试雇用他们，是的
sort of an alternative it's older than
比它早一些的替代方案
OAuth 2 at least anyway it isn't it
OAuth 2至少不是这样
isn't a standard it has a few slightly
不是标准，它有一些
different features but if you want to
不同的功能，但如果您想
run a single sign-on system and it it's
运行一个单一的登录系统，它是
it's an interesting starting point it's
这是一个有趣的起点
very heavily integrated with spring so
与弹簧高度集成，因此
it's a nice nice platform to use with
这是一个很好的平台
spring apps as well it's I started I
春天的应用程序也是我开始
know I'm literally recently but it used
知道我真的是最近，但是它用过
to be as there's a little bit more
因为还有更多
chatter involved between the server
服务器之间涉及的不休
components then sort of dinner later
组件然后晚饭
water-tube there is basically the same
水管基本上是一样的
features roughly speaking tokens and
具有大致讲代币的功能
trusts and
信任和
single sign-on and that kind of thing
单点登录之类的事情
you out it del okay gotcha
你出去吧，好吧
- seems to be popular and you know
-似乎很受欢迎，你知道
social media and some somewhat any
社交媒体和一些
otherwise CAF oh yeah this meta mainly
否则CAF哦，是的，这个meta主要是
has a foothold in the academic community
在学术界立足
interesting I didn't realize that okay
有趣的是我没意识到
huh interesting
呵呵有趣
alright um see a bernard o'neill asks
好吧，嗯，看到伯纳德·奥尼尔问
for x.509 would you use the same process
对于x.509，您是否会使用相同的过程
with a gateway for validating this sort
与用于验证这种类型的网关
of generating a cookie I would yeah
我会生成一个cookie的
because that's actually something that's
因为那实际上是
quite tricky to configure he wouldn't
配置他不会很棘手
want to do it in all of the backend
想要在所有后端中做到这一点
components unless you did that routine
组件，除非您执行了该例程
anyway but it's a single point of
无论如何，但这只是
controllers now so yeah probably within
控制器现在如此，可能在
that way um Ramesh asks hi if the
那样拉姆尼什问你好
request is routed to the UI plus
请求被路由到UI plus
resource through gateway or UI plus
通过网关或UI加上资源
resource excuse me that was the label
资源对不起，那是标签
and I was a label I put on one of the
我是一个标签，贴在其中一个
boxes yeah yeah okay sorry okay cool
盒子是是好的抱歉好的酷
critical area so it if the request is
关键区域，如果请求是
being paid yeah yep so if the request is
是的，是的，如果请求是
routed the UI plus resource through
路由UI加资源通过
gateway and the Gateway sits on port
网关，网关位于端口上
8080 and the app is running on port 8080
8080，并且该应用程序在端口8080上运行
one will it be across the main request
主要需求之一
you know don't see any of this well I
你知道看不到任何我
mean it would be if it came from the
意思是如果它来自
browser to port 8081 but it doesn't
浏览器到端口8081，但没有
right it goes through the proxy so the
对，它通过代理，所以
proxy basically means that you control
代理基本上意味着您可以控制
the common origin that is a common
共同的起源
origin it's all coming through the proxy
起源全部通过代理
so that's a good thing I didn't mention
所以我没有提到这是一件好事
it I see
我明白了
except in passing that common origin
除了通过共同的起源
resource sharing a heads it's like I
资源共享的头就像我
said at the beginning it's in the
说开始时它在
browser you should use the feature but
浏览器，您应该使用该功能，但是
actually implementing it in the server
实际上在服务器上实现它
side there's a little bit tricky and
侧面有些棘手，
people get it wrong all the time so it's
人们总是会出错，所以
a good thing if you don't have to do it
一件好事，如果您不必这样做
that's one reason one of the main
这是主要原因之一
reasons I like this proxy fast and
我快速喜欢此代理的原因，
actually because that means I don't have
实际上是因为那意味着我没有
that headache I don't have to worry
头疼我不用担心
about it I've done it right
关于它，我做对了
I don't have to explicitly list all of
我不必明确列出所有
the API resources for instance in my
API资源，例如
common origin so I can you know I can
共同的血统，所以我可以知道
break up the back ends in any way in any
以任何方式破坏后端
any way I like and I don't have to
我喜欢的任何方式，我都不必
change the configuration of the cause
更改原因的配置
filters on the clients cool well I seem
客户端上的过滤器看起来不错
to have open open the floodgates for for
为...打开水闸
questions there's a cub watch coming in
问题是有一只幼崽手表进来了
now um let's see uh Eli or Ellie
现在，让我们来看看Eli或Ellie
depending on how he likes to pronounce
取决于他喜欢如何发音
his name asks does zoo support websocket
他的名字问动物园是否支持websocket
proxy somebody else asked me this no I
代理人问我这个不，我
don't think so because it's based on the
不要这么认为，因为它基于
servlet API this is version 1 right so
Servlet API，这是版本1，所以
everything in the net fix back is under
网络修复中的所有内容都在下面
development for version 2 basically in
版本2的开发基本上在
Zul version 2 is not tied to service and
Zul版本2与服务无关，
it's more stringent based and I'm pretty
比较严格，我很漂亮
sure it will support not just WebSockets
确保它不仅支持WebSockets
to basically TCP so we'll end up using
基本上是TCP，所以我们最终将使用
that at some point but it's not ready as
在某个时候，但还没有准备好
a minute I think it's probably sort of a
一分钟，我认为可能是
late 2015 in production 2016 kind of
2015年底于2016年投产
thing got it okay and that's from the
事情还好，那是从
Netflix side the right to their your own
Netflix拥有自己的权利
work ok very well we I mean we're pretty
很好，工作很好，我是说我们很漂亮
heavily involved in some of that stuff
大量参与其中的某些事情
now so yeah I imagine there will be
现在，是的，我想将会有
women webinars coming later on this year
女性网络研讨会将于今年晚些时候举行
about some stuff that other people are
关于别人的一些东西
doing in that scrap um but yeah it's
在那废料中做，但是是的
it's - basically it's sort of breaking
-基本上是一种突破
the mold in terms of concerns of
考虑到模具
protocols for well not just protocol the
协议不仅适用于协议
API support awesome ok yeah yeah
API支持很棒，是的，是的
definitely I've been I've been noodling
肯定我一直在闲逛
around thinking about that exact same
围绕着完全相同的思考
thing wondering if we should start
想知道我们是否应该开始
inviting some of the Netflix folks to
邀请一些Netflix员工参加
present yeah you think you called it
现在是的，你认为你叫它
there
那里
Stefan asks is there a security risk in
Stefan询问是否存在安全隐患
the use of JavaScript containing the
包含
rest endpoints for these projects versus
这些项目的其余端点与
the classic web projects
经典的网络项目
well I can read I can read that again if
好吧，我可以阅读，如果可以，我可以再次阅读
you like no I mean I'm just an island
你不喜欢我是说我只是一个小岛
for the second yes maybe Rob has some
对于第二个，也许罗布有一些
comments that a more incisive and or
评论更尖锐和或
insightful and mine that I think the
有见地和我的，我认为
floodgate is a for basically I mean the
水闸基本上是因为
the the door has the horse of definitely
门肯定有马
both on that on anyway because these
无论如何，因为这些
single page applications are just so
单页应用程序就是这样
ubiquitous because users like and I
无处不在，因为用户喜欢我
don't think you'd be able to put that
不要以为你能把那个
genie back in a bottle even if you
精灵回到瓶子里，即使你
wanted to but um I'm trying to think
想但是我想
what could be the problem I mean but
我的意思是什么问题，但是
really that suppose that's what common
真的，那是常见的
origin resource sharing is supposed to
原始资源共享应该
address isn't it I mean there are
地址是不是我的意思是有
security risks involved in clients
客户涉及的安全风险
accessing um you know resources that are
存取您知道的资源
not completely static but if you want if
不是完全静态的，但是如果您想
you want user to be able to do anything
您希望用户能够执行任何操作
non-trivial you sort of let them do it
不平凡的你让他们去做
it's just a question of how you control
这只是您如何控制的问题
the reactor so cause is one answer to
反应堆的原因是
the question and the the physical
问题和身体
locations of the back-end resources that
后端资源的位置
she shared with the clients at all if
她与客户分享
you don't really that's another
你不是真的那是另一回事
advantage of having a proxy not just
拥有代理的优势不只是
that well I mean the front end doesn't
好吧，我的意思是前端不
have to know about the structure of the
必须知道的结构
backend at all it can all be completely
完全可以是后端
dynamic which I like and in addition to
我喜欢并且除了动态
being secure so I don't know quite what
是安全的，所以我不太清楚
security may be it may be I didn't think
安全可能是我没想到
of the security risk that the original
原来的安全隐患
question was aimed at that that seems to
问题似乎是针对
be yeah still I can think over the
是的，我仍然可以考虑
spearmint place anyway in this no
留兰香的地方无论如何
worries yeah um I'll let him jump in on
担心，嗯，我会让他跳进去
that shot if he has something to
如果他有什么要
something to add um let's see okay
要添加一些东西，让我们看看还好吧
I did it to do there with my first
我第一次这样做是为了做到这一点
second David sorry I kind of lost my
第二个大卫对不起，我有点迷失了自己
place a little bit there okay here we go
放一点，好吧，我们去
um
嗯
great yeah Rob's jumping in on that that
是的，Rob跳进去了
CAS question from from earlier Bernard
来自早期Bernard的CAS问题
O'Neil asks so for x.509 would you use
O'Neil要求使用x.509
the same process with the Gateway
与网关相同的过程
validating the cert and generating a
验证证书并生成一个
cookie I think you already asked me that
cookie，我想你已经问过我
question I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm
问题我很抱歉我很抱歉我
so sorry I did ask you did I did ask
对不起，我确实问过你，我确实问过
that one I'm so sorry um I guess I
那个我很抱歉，我猜我
didn't still did lose my place okay had
仍然没有失去我的位置好了
a question on ntlm authentication that
有关ntlm身份验证的问题
Rob handled here we go Praveen Kumar
罗布处理了这里，我们去了普拉文·库玛
asks how is the authorization supporting
请问授权如何支持
microservices using spring cloud would
使用Spring Cloud的微服务将
it be along the lines of a single micro
沿着一个微型的路线
service which takes care of
照顾的服务
authorization and other micro service
授权和其他微服务
hits this authorization service that was
点击此授权服务
my that was that picture right so you
我那是那张照片，所以你
could do it that way well you could just
可以那样做就可以了
build all of your authentication into
将所有身份验证构建到
the Gateway I think it's really out so
网关，我认为它真的出局了
it's up to you that's the beauty of this
这取决于你，这就是美丽
pattern right because it's a full fully
模式正确，因为它是完整的
loaded spring application in the Gateway
在网关中加载的Spring应用程序
you can do whatever you want in it
你可以在里面做任何你想做的
yeah I mean did you know I think when he
是的，我是说你知道我在想什么时候他
went so when he said when Praveen says
当他说Praveen说的时候去了
micro services in his question I assume
我认为他的问题中的微服务
that that means he's thinking about some
那意味着他正在考虑一些
sort of machine to machine headless you
有点机器让你无头
know kind of kind of app profile and but
知道某种类型的应用程序配置文件，但是
I don't think that would really change
我认为那真的不会改变
your answer right I mean you might want
您的回答正确，我的意思是您可能想要
to know well I mean if it works then
要知道，我的意思是，如果这样的话
yeah then then you can use oauth2 to get
是的，那么您可以使用oauth2来获取
tokens that's one thing you can do and
令牌是您可以做的一件事，
or you can use you know the user
或者您可以使用您认识的用户
accounts that represent machines instead
代表机器的帐户
of users and just use normal
的用户，并且只使用普通
Authenticator other normal
身份验证器其他正常
authentication channels but generally
身份验证渠道，但通常
speaking in these applications you've
在这些应用程序中发言
got a user driving all the operations
让用户来驱动所有操作
right so even if it's offline a user is
对，所以即使用户离线
responsible for every action of taking
负责采取的每项行动
it so you kind of want to associate
所以你有点想联系
every request with a user initially
最初与用户的每个请求
especially in this single page
特别是在这一页中
application it's not I've been talking
应用程序不是我一直在谈论
about excellent all-righty Alexius I'm
关于优秀的全能Alexius我
not going to try to save last name
不会尝试保存姓氏
because I think I'm really gonna get it
因为我想我真的会得到它
wrong um
错了
Alexia's asks if we're developing behind
Alexia问我们是否在落后
a load balancer for example NLB what
负载均衡器（例如NLB）
issues could we expect when using Zul
使用Zul时我们可以预期的问题
any any Col use selling benefits quote
任何使用Col的销售利益报价
again there I mean I've been using Saul
再一次，我是说我一直在使用扫罗
behind the load balancer a lot right
在负载均衡器后面很多
because I use it in Cloud Foundry all
因为我在Cloud Foundry全部使用它
the time I haven't seen anything
我什么都没看见的时候
difficult about it yet but I mean I know
很难，但我是说我知道
that proxies can mess with HTTP so you
代理可能会与HTTP混淆，因此您
can win anything anything nefarious
可以赢得任何邪恶的东西
could a proxy could plead to screw you
代理人可以恳求把你搞砸
up it it probably probably might at some
可能在某些情况下
point I don't see anything obvious that
我看不到任何明显的东西
would happen as long as the proxies well
只要代理很好就会发生
behaved and passes all the headers
表现并传递所有标题
through and that kind of thing yeah I
通过这样的事情，是的，我
mean I I've used it extensively but and
意思是我已经广泛使用了它，但是
I haven't noticed any problems that's
我没有发现任何问题
all I can say
我只能说
got it okay processing yeah props you
知道了，可以处理道具
screw with her so he could it could do
和她拧在一起，他可以做到
all sorts of things that might might
可能会发生的各种事情
throw a spanner in the works but I don't
在作品中扔一个扳手，但我不
seen any specific examples here
在这里看到任何具体的例子
I feel these things well hopefully you
我希望你感觉很好
can obviously with those things in Zoo
显然可以与Zoo中的那些东西
because it's highly programmable I say
因为它是高度可编程的
if you know what to expect in your
如果你知道你期望什么
property as long as there's not you know
财产，只要你不知道
removing information that you can't get
删除您无法获取的信息
back then you can probably manipulate
那时你可能可以操纵
things got it
事情得到了
okay Oh interesting okay so Zul is
好的，很有趣，所以祖尔是
pretty customizable in that way too
也可以以这种方式自定义
interesting alright um let's see ah
有趣的好吧，让我们看看啊
later Reza asks um how are we going to
后来Reza问嗯我们要如何
integrate springs social later into a
将springs social整合到以后
single page presume you mean the
单页假定您的意思是
application I suppose what he means is
我想他的意思是
again going back to the picture that's
再次回到那张图片
on the screen now spring social would be
在屏幕上现在春季社交将是
calling out to you know Facebook or
呼唤您知道Facebook或
YouTube or something as an old server
YouTube或旧服务器
instead of instead of your own
而不是你自己的
implementation things fundamentally I
从根本上来说，实现的东西
mean it just changes the way you
意味着它只是改变了你的方式
implement security in the Gateway it
在网关中实现安全性
doesn't change very much it's just a
不会有太大变化，只是
spring security trick right to change
Spring Security 技巧改变的权利
the authentication source and sometimes
身份验证源，有时
the only gift the only difficult thing
唯一的礼物，唯一的困难
really sometimes it's just making the
确实有时候，
user experience acceptable because you
用户体验可以接受，因为您
know users sort of have to choose if
知道用户必须选择是否
you've got more than one authentication
您已获得多个身份验证
source how do you get the easier to
资料来源，您如何变得更容易
choose which one to use that you know
选择您知道使用哪个
some some people can't be trusted to
有些人无法信任
choose certain height authentication
选择一定的身高认证
source for instance and then you've got
例如来源，然后
a problem
一个问题
but if you can Nina if you can do it in
但是如果你可以的话，妮娜
spring security you can do it in a
Spring Security ，您可以在一个
gateway because it's just a spring
网关，因为这只是春天
security application okay so we're about
安全应用程序好，所以我们即将
seven after I think we have time for
七点之后，我认为我们有时间
just a couple couple more questions and
再问几个问题，
fortunately it looks like that's all
幸运的是，看起来就这样
that remains which is quite nice Jeremy
仍然很不错杰里米
holter asks hello the risk regarding
霍尔特问你好有关的风险
security wait a minute on I gotta read
安全，请稍等，我必须阅读
this again
再来一次
oh boy um
哦，男孩，嗯
okay all right
好吧好吧
oh okay so he's he's concerned about the
哦好吧，所以他是他担心的
risk of a denial-of-service attack by
拒绝服务攻击的风险
somebody analyzing the rest service that
有人分析了其他服务
was called right do you feel like that's
被称为正确，你觉得那是
a kitchen comment on that maybe risk of
厨房评论说可能有
that perhaps yeah I mean if you open up
也许是的，我的意思是如果你打开
a resource to the Internet then it's
互联网资源，然后
obviously vulnerable to that sort of
显然很容易受到这种伤害
thing I mean I suppose the only thing I
我的意思是我想唯一的一件事
would say is that if you have a gateway
会说，如果您有网关
a programmable gateway like we do the
像我们这样的可编程网关
examples I was just showing then you can
我刚刚展示的例子，那么你可以
do things like rate-limiting and you
做限速之类的事情，你
know you can deal with some common
知道你可以应付一些共同点
denial of service sectors just through
仅仅通过拒绝服务部门
the Gateway itself which is very
网关本身
interesting is definitely the way that
有趣的绝对是
it gets used in their fix
它被用于修复
got it I mean the browser needs to
知道了，我的意思是浏览器需要
contact API resources the browser needs
联系浏览器需要的API资源
to contact a Pheo resources so you know
与Pheo资源联系，以便您知道
you just have to somehow find a way of
您只需要以某种方式找到一种方法
dealing with that thing rate limiting is
处理那个速率限制是
one of the ones one of the things that
其中之一
people do I imagine that there might be
人们会不会想到
some demand for that as a features frame
作为功​​能框架的一些需求
filed in fact you could implement it
提起您实际上可以实施
really simply already would still but
真的已经可以了
it's such a common use case that I think
我认为这是一个非常常见的用例
the we might added to spring cloud at
我们可能会在
some point if there's any demand awesome
如果有很棒的需求
getting a feature request set of webinar
获取网络研讨会的功能请求集
attendees yay
参加者
love it um okay let's see yeah okay um
喜欢它，好吧，让我们看看吧，好吧，嗯
Alexius you already had a question my
Alexius你已经有一个问题我的
friends so long let me make sure I get
朋友这么久让我确保我得到
to the remainder oh wait a minute sorry
剩下的哦，等等，对不起
we did and we did answer that okay
我们做到了，我们确实回答了
weird stuff showing up out of port here
奇怪的东西出现在港口外
ah here we go um II Eva Eva yeah Eva
啊，在这里，我们去吧II Eva Eva是啊Eva
asks
问
IVA Elanco asks hi what's the best
IVA Elanco问嗨，什么是最好的
policy to use access control allow
使用访问控制的策略允许
origin header with a spring app I think
我认为带有春季应用程序的原始标头
Rob already posted a link actually into
Rob已经实际发布了一个链接到
the chat and it's not flying by there's
聊天，它没有飞过
a spring issue in JIRA and to do is
JIRA的春季刊，要做的是
spring support for common erosion which
春季支持常见侵蚀
is what you're talking about it's a
你在说的是
there are many ways basically most
基本上有很多方法
people these days just write a filter
这些天的人只是写一个过滤器
and they're quiet they you know quite
他们很安静，你知道的
sort of it's a bit of a blunt instrument
有点太钝了
they're quite happy to do things in a
他们很高兴在
very simple way or as actually it's a
非常简单的方法，或者实际上是
bit more subtle and I think with Rob and
更加微妙，我认为与Rob和
Russell working together I think you'll
罗素一起工作，我想你会
see something coming out of spring ins
看到春天来了
but hopefully in spring 4.2 if spring
但希望在春季4.2，如果春季
security for point something there'll be
安全点的东西
more granting of supporter access
支持者更多的访问权限
solution something yes okay so one of
解决的东西是好的，所以其中之一
the samples that I did in the blog has a
我在博客中所做的样本有一个
filter that does this but it's very
过滤器可以做到这一点，但这非常
crude and I put a big health warning on
原油，我在上面发出了很大的健康警告
it do not use this in production got it
它没有在生产中使用它
I'm sorry yes and Rob actually did
很抱歉，Rob确实做到了
answer that my apology so I think were I
回答我的道歉，所以我想我是
think we are at and here did you did
认为我们在，你在这里做了
today
今天
okay we're close actually there's two
好的，我们要关闭了，实际上有两个
two questions left up three um but we're
还有两个问题三个um，但我们
just about out of time on Dave are you
戴夫几乎没时间了
okay with maybe two more minutes to
还可以再等两分钟
attend to these last two questions so so
参加最后两个问题，如此
that all right okay okay great um let's
好的，好的，太好了，让我们
see so on Praveen
在Praveen上看到
again Praveen Kumar yeah and asks so how
再次Praveen Kumar是，并问如何
is the authorisation supporting micro
是授权支持微
services using spring cloud would it be
使用Spring Cloud的服务会是
along the line wait a minute yeah oh
沿线等一下哦
yeah yeah I think we had that one done I
是的，我想我们做了一个
seem to be coming out twice some of
好像要出来两次
these questions yeah I think people are
这些问题是的，我认为人们是
just trying to pop to the front of the
只是试图弹出到
stack and they're they're putting them
堆，他们正在把他们
on twice on okay anyway sorry about that
两次就可以了
probably just not very responsive if
如果可能的话，可能只是反应不太快
somebody types a question and I don't
有人问一个问题，我不
see it immediately they'll probably just
立即看到它们，他们可能只会
type it again
再打一遍
yeah I think this is exactly what's
是的，我认为这正是
happening okay Abhijit Abhijit asks how
发生的一切都很好Abhijit Abhijit问如何
do you normally deploy the angular
你通常部署角度
application um you know since a normal
你知道一个正常的应用程序
angular act would only have static
角度动作只会具有静态
content you know do we really need a war
您知道我们真的需要打仗吗
yeah so I don't have a wall right I just
是的，所以我没有隔离墙
in my apps I just have static resources
在我的应用程序中，我只有静态资源
it's um yeah I mean there's if I didn't
是的，是的，我是说如果没有
have a gateway there might be some
有一个网关可能会有一些
reasons for keeping dynamic resources
保留动态资源的原因
around because I need to change the URLs
因为我需要更改URL
of the backends things like that but
像这样的后端
with a gateway there really isn't any
有了网关，实际上没有任何网关
any problem with just deploying static
只是部署静态的任何问题
HTML and JavaScript which is all it was
HTML和JavaScript就这样
in the samples even in production
在样品中甚至在生产中
alright and you said you were running
好吧，你说你正在跑步
this on spring boot right Dave
戴夫（Dave）的 spring boot
am I going nuts yeah yeah say I could
我疯了吗，是的，我可以
easily off I if I needed it but I didn't
如果需要，可以轻松离开我，但我没有
really right right yeah I remember I
是的，是的，我记得我
love shortly after spring boot came out
spring boot 出来后不久的爱
I remember seeing a blog post about how
我记得看过一篇关于如何
to do static resources with with boot so
用启动做静态资源
I know that's yeah really said one
我知道那是真的
didn't I yeah yeah um okay I think last
我不是，是啊，嗯，我想最后
question then and the other one the
然后问题，另一个
other last question is looks like it's
最后一个问题是
getting handled by um bye bye Rob or or
被um bye bye Rob或or处理
Thorsten so last question I think before
托尔斯滕，我想过的最后一个问题
we shut it down um
我们把它关闭了
oh boy cou Jen Jen say Oh a COO Jen kay
哦，男孩cou Jen Jen说哦，COO Jen kay
asks how would you integrate
问你如何整合
authenticate with Facebook Twitter like
通过Facebook Twitter进行身份验证，例如
functionality with off already
功能已关闭
implemented in the related spring social
在相关的春季社交中实施
project I think we kind of answered this
项目我想我们已经回答了这个
earlier mmm
较早的mmm
sort of yeah I mean I said I was gonna
是的，我是说我要
put it in the Gateway so in the Gateway
放在网关中，这样在网关中
you could just link your Facebook or
您可以只链接您的Facebook或
whatever um you know use a resource to
不管你知道用什么资源
the spring security context and then
Spring Security 上下文，然后
you're you finished basically there are
你基本上完成了
already some projects out there that do
已经有一些项目在做
that that um integrate the spring social
那个整合了春季社会
stack with the spring security filter
与弹簧安全过滤器叠放
and actually spring cloud security has
实际上，Spring Cloud安全性具有
some features to support that as well
一些功能也支持
out on the books declaratively but um
声明式地在书上出来，但嗯
it's just more than one way to do that
这不只是一种实现方法
in the Gateway alright folks
在门户好人
we'll listen thank you so much for the
我们会非常感谢您的
time the question the attention all all
时间问题大家的关注
the questions Dave great job thanks so
戴夫的问题很好，谢谢
much I know this is this blog post
我很清楚这是此博客文章
series has just been you know super
系列只是你知道超级
popular lately so on this fantastic we
最近流行，所以在这个梦幻般的我们
are recording this session and it will
正在录制此会话，它将
be posted to spring dot IO /video which
被发布到spring dot IO / video
is our YouTube channel on or if you also
是我们的YouTube频道吗？
if you subscribe to the atom feed on
如果您订阅原子饲料
spring Gallo blog you should get you'll
春天的加洛博客，你应该得到你的
get a you'll get a notification when we
当我们收到通知时，您会收到通知
when we post this I'm trying to plug
当我们发布这个时，我试图插入
this to URLs into the chat window right
URL到聊天窗口中
now and it's there we go okay
现在，在那里我们可以了
so if you scroll to the bottom of the
因此，如果您滚动到
chat window you'll see the two links for
聊天窗口中，您将看到两个链接
spring arrow blog explaining our video
春天箭头博客解释我们的视频
recommend if you want to notice about
建议您是否要注意
when it's what's posted that you
当它是什么张贴你
subscribe to the atom feed for our blog
订阅我们博客的原子供稿
because then you'll also get all the
因为那样你也会得到所有
great content from engineering and
工程学和
spring one replays you know accessory
春季重播，你知道配件
cetera et cetera so lots of good stuff
等等等等很多好东西
there obviously if you had been
显然如果你去过那里
subscribed you would have already seen
订阅您将已经看到
Dave's blog because it was originally
Dave的博客，因为它最初是
published there it's wonderful um let's
在那里发布了，真是太好了，让我们
see I think we'd love to have you come
看，我想我们很想让你来
back oh yes
回来哦，是的
you can also Alexis just us you can get
你也可以Alexis就是我们你可以得到
it with Twitter if you follow us at
如果您关注我们，请使用Twitter
Spring Central um you can also see you
春天中央，嗯，你也可以看到你
know I usually usually post a tweet when
知道我通常在什么时候发布推文
the replays available but if you want
重播可用，但如果您要
the absolute guarantee I would sign up
我会签约的绝对保证
for the blog every once in a while I
偶尔我会写博客
don't tweet about a replay but that's an
不要发布有关重播的推文，但这是
exception and not the rule so great
例外而不是那么大的规则
so speaking of webinars on please join
所以说到网络研讨会，请加入
us again if you if you like this topic
如果您喜欢此主题，请再次与我们联系
Scott dig from our field is going to be
我们领域的Scott挖矿将是
hosting another
主持另一个
aw he was so inspired by Dave's blog
哇，他深受Dave博客的启发
series that he's actually going to going
他实际上要去的系列
to basically do what Dave did although
基本上做了戴夫所做的
with a polymer front-end so if you're if
带有聚合物前端，如果
you're you know into a different
你知道你进入了另一个世界
JavaScript front-end for your single
您的单曲的JavaScript前端
page application on polymer might give
聚合物上的页面应用程序可能会给
you a yeah that's kind of a latest web
是的，这是最新的网络
framework out of Google right so my
Google提供的框架，所以我的
exact that out I'm gonna get to that
确切地说，我要去那个
yeah totally I know I'm kind of curious
是的，我知道我很好奇
to see the differences myself so yeah
自己看看差异，是的
he's he's pretty excited about that one
他对那个感到非常兴奋
as well so that's on February 20 excuse
也就是2月20日的借口
me that's on March 24th
我是3月24日
um so please feel free to join us there
嗯，请随时加入我们的行列
I'm going to plug the URL for the
我要插入网址
registration on into the chat window as
在聊天窗口中注册为
well on should be there towards the
那么应该朝着
bottom let's see hold on let's try it
底部，让我们看看坚持吧，尝试一下
again
再次
yes Philippe we should have a Facebook
是的，菲利普，我们应该有一个Facebook
page in fact we do you go on Facebook
页面，事实上，您在Facebook上吗
you look for spring sources you will
您寻找弹簧源，您将
find a group that was not started by us
找到一个不是我们发起的小组
but is partially managed by us as well
但也由我们部分管理
and then whenever I do post tweets a
然后每当我发布推文
link will actually go out to those
链接实际上将转到那些
Facebook pages so um so the other
脸书网页好多了
webinar that's upcoming on a bit of a
即将举行的网络研讨会
different topic although I'm still
尽管我仍然不同
angular and still JavaScript front-end
有角度的JavaScript前端
Josh long and Julian Dubois are going to
乔什·朗（Josh Long）和朱利安·杜波依（Julian Dubois）将要
join up and they're going to be
参加，他们将成为
introducing J hipster which is a yeoman
介绍约曼的J时髦
generator for angularjs and spring
用于angularjs和spring的生成器
spring boot very cool little app
spring boot 非常酷的小应用程序
generator and that's going to be on
发电机，这将继续
March 17th
3月17日
so next next Tuesday so please do join
所以下个星期二所以请加入
us for that um I am attempting to find
我们试图找到那个
the URL so I can plug it into the window
URL，以便我可以将其插入窗口
for you I thought I had it but I guess
为你，我以为我有，但我猜
it's I'm actually looking at the blog um
我实际上是在看博客
so ah the last thing I'll just mention
所以啊，我最后要提的是
is that generally speaking if you're
通常来说，如果你是
looking to get a hold of
希望获得
bits for first you know for any sort of
首先，你知道任何形式的
spring project just realize that we have
春季项目只是意识到我们有
not enabled HTTP downloads on on spring
春季未启用HTTP下载
Iowa website it's just a horrible
爱荷华州的网站，这简直是可怕
experience for developers really that
开发人员的经验真的
much better to use maven or Gradle but
使用Maven或Gradle更好，但是
yet we understand that some of you are
但是我们知道你们中有些人
on military networks or closed networks
在军事网络或封闭网络上
or behind 50 layers of proxy servers and
或位于50层以下的代理服务器和
so for that reason you can get ahold of
因此，您可以
HTTP downloads for various spring
各种春季的HTTP下载
projects at reap repo spring bio it's
在reap repo spring bio的项目是
certainly not in you know we don't try
当然不在您知道我们不会尝试
to make that experience easy let's say
让我们轻松体验
but but they are available so if you
但它们可用，所以如果您
really really really need HTTP downloads
真的真的真的需要HTTP下载
week weekend fun for you on that then
周末周末在那为你带来乐趣
that's where to find them let's see
那是找到他们的地方，让我们看看
almost got that J hipster URL which I
几乎得到了我的J时髦URL
think it's going to be a fun one and
认为这会很有趣，
seen you having some trouble finding it
看到您在找到它时遇到一些麻烦
but anyway if you look around in the
但是无论如何，如果你环顾四周
spring site you will see that that that
春季现场，您将看到
webinars next should be next Tuesday for
网络研讨会下一个应该在下周二举行
J hipster so Dave thank you very much
J时髦所以Dave非常感谢你
great great talk a lot of positive
很棒的很棒的演讲非常积极
feedback in the chat to a lot of people
聊天中反馈给很多人
saying thanks and great presentation so
说谢谢和很棒的演讲
I just want to let you know that and
我只想让你知道
anything you want to say before we kind
在我们友善之前你想说的任何话
of close it out and take it home for the
将其关闭并将其带回家
day thank you all right wonderful
谢谢你，美好的一天
on see you next time everyone have a
下次大家见面时
great day bye-bye
美好的一天再见